<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/anthony-s-blog/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/anthony-s-blog/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-06-17T10:45:28-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/anthony-s-blog/feed.xml</id><entry><title type="html">Part 6</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/anthony-s-blog/part-6" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Part 6" /><published>2021-06-16T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2021-06-16T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/anthony-s-blog/part%206</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/anthony-s-blog/part-6">&lt;h1 id=&quot;anthonys-blog&quot;&gt;Anthony’s Blog&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anthony’s Adventures Around ISD!
—&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;title: Day 6!
date:  2021-06-16&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hi. Did you miss me?? It’s the sixth day in the ISD department. I successed and falied somewhat today. Coding my blog is going okay. Good news is everything is coming at great! The bad news is I can’t put a theme on it. So, it might stay plain white for a couple days. We’re troubleshooting now but no luck. The day has hasn’t been all day though! My blog is complete… somewhat. The site is still a little buggy, but everything else is working fine. I got my second monitor working! I always had it at my desk but I didn’t know how to set it up. But, I got it now! It’s pretty cool. Next, I might get a light to show I’m in a meeting. I don’t know why, maybe because everyone else in the office has one so I want one haha. Well, the last hour of work is almost over. Anthony out! Oh yeah, that’s gonna stick! -Anthony&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Anthony</name></author><summary type="html">Anthony’s Blog Anthony’s Adventures Around ISD! —</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Part 5</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/anthony-s-blog/part-5" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Part 5" /><published>2021-06-15T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2021-06-15T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/anthony-s-blog/part%205</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/anthony-s-blog/part-5">&lt;h1 id=&quot;anthonys-blog&quot;&gt;Anthony’s Blog&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anthony’s Adventures Around ISD!
—&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;title: Day 5!
date:  2021-06-15
—&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hi guys! It’s Anthony! So day 5 aready… time flies. I progessed WAY MORE than usual today. I have learned more coding to get my site up and functional as possible. It’s been really fun! At first, I thought I wouldn’t be able be put up coding. And to my suprise… I’m actually getting it. Yeah, there are some hiccups here and there but for the most point, I’m learning pretty quickly. I can’t wait to make my blog site. The more I learn, the more I can cumstomize the site! It’s not even half done yet but I’m getting closer to it everyday. And that’s it for today. Anthony out! Ok, admit it… DO YOU LIKE IT OR NOT? -Anthony&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Anthony</name></author><summary type="html">Anthony’s Blog Anthony’s Adventures Around ISD! —</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Part 4</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/anthony-s-blog/part-4" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Part 4" /><published>2021-06-14T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2021-06-14T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/anthony-s-blog/part%204</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/anthony-s-blog/part-4">&lt;h1 id=&quot;anthonys-blog&quot;&gt;Anthony’s Blog&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anthony’s Adventures Around ISD!
—&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;title: Day 4!
date: 2021-06-14
—&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My second week at KUB begins! Today was mostly spent on this blog! I learned to how to set the website so I can put all my entries on it. I hit a wall but I’m gonna keep on it! I had a lot of help today. The people here are very helpful even when they think they can’t help me much. It’s a big relief because I know I have people that can lead me a hand. Ok, that wraps it up! Anthony out! Still not used to that yet… -Anthony&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Anthony</name></author><summary type="html">Anthony’s Blog Anthony’s Adventures Around ISD! —</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Part 3</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/anthony-s-blog/part-3" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Part 3" /><published>2021-06-10T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2021-06-10T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/anthony-s-blog/part%203</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/anthony-s-blog/part-3">&lt;h1 id=&quot;anthonys-blog&quot;&gt;Anthony’s Blog&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anthony’s Adventures Around ISD!
—&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;title: Day 3!
date:  2021-06-10
—&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today was pretty short. I only worked three hours today!. Since I’m an TeenWorker, I only can work 24 hours a week. So no overtime or things like that. Today, I got back to the WorkStation setup. It was a little easier than yesterday but I still asked Madison some questions. Lastly, I learned some basic commands for Git Bash. I went over a tutorial Madison sent me. She told to watch it and learn as many of the commands as I could. Some I knew and some I didn’t. I’m not finished yet because I had to started my blog! I promised myself I would find how to end of my posts and I think I found something I like! Well I only have an hour left. So Anthony out! Do you like it?? I kinda do and to be honest, that’s the best it’s going to get haha.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Anthony</name></author><summary type="html">Anthony’s Blog Anthony’s Adventures Around ISD! —</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Part 2</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/anthony-s-blog/part-2" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Part 2" /><published>2021-06-09T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2021-06-09T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/anthony-s-blog/part%202</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/anthony-s-blog/part-2">&lt;h1 id=&quot;anthonys-blog&quot;&gt;Anthony’s Blog&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hello again, it’s Anthony!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anthony’s Adventures Around ISD!
title: Day 2!
date: 2021-06-9
 Today was my second day at KUB. I was mostly at my desk today because my computer is completly fixed. I learned a decent amount today. I began setting up my Workstation setup. No, not my desk. It was all on the computer! I had to download A LOT of apps. It had to be at least 7 apps. It was very diffcult and tricky, but half way done with it. It takes a couple days so I’ll be doing it for a minute. After that, I got started on learning HTML! HTML is basically the building blocks of a website. This is where the words, descriptions, photos, and videos from a website comes from. I also learned some of the basic code for HTML. Once I get more knowledge on HTML, I should be able to work my blog in it! This job is really eye-opening for me I say. I struggled today a bit but, everyday isn’t going to be easy and I shouldn’t except it to be either. But still a good day nethertheless! Last hour of work is writing for my blog and it’s slwoing becoming my favorite part of the day. I still gotta learn to end this thing, so see you next time! -Anthony&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Anthony</name></author><summary type="html">Anthony’s Blog Hello again, it’s Anthony!</summary></entry></feed>